VINCCI TSUI

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

ABOUT

I am a web developer with design experience. I am currently work daily with React, JavaScript, Node, git, webpack, HTML and SASS. I am also currently learning TypeScript. I find the middle ground of functionality, aesthetics, and user experience. As a believer in universal design, I consider user experience and accessibility as I code.

CONTACT

Email: vinccimantsui@gmail.com

Cell: +1 647 286 4800

Portfolio: www.vinccitsui.me

github.com/vt1022

linkedin.com/in/vinccimantsui/

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Engineer | Coates Group | 2021 - present

- Primarily worked with React, Redux, Sass, JavaScript. Occasionally used TypeScript
- Brought new features to life from ideation to final product using tools such as React hooks, functional components and styled components
- Conducted weekly 1 on 1 knowledge share sessions with junior developers
- Trained new team members on JavaScript and CSS best practices and common debugging processes
- Worked with design team to prototype and deliver time-sensitive projects for McDonald's Canada

Junior Frontend Developer | Coates Group | 2020 - 2021

- Worked extensively with Sass and React to map out dynamic content
- Used CSS to style captivating menu boards for McDonald's Canada
- Fetched data from internal database to be displayed on the menus
- Solved compatibility issues caused by required support of older browser versions
- · Worked closely with QA, CMS, and Design team in an agile environment

Freelance | Che Patisserie | www.chepatisserie.com | 2021

- e-Commerce website designed and developed for small bakery selling weekly products
- Used mobile-first best practices to align with the usage patterns of majority end-users
- Pulls data from Google Sheets to simplify content management for non-technical client
- Leveraged EmailJS to send automated confirmation/invoice emails to customers
- Integrated Discord webhooks to send notifications to business owner when an order is submitted

PROJECTS

PokeMatch| jQuery, Sass | vt1022.github.io/pokematch/

- A memory game to match pairs of face down Pokemon cards
- Flexbox and media queries for responsive design
- Tabindex property to ensure accessibility
- Built with BEM and Sass

SKILLS

React	Node
JavaScript	Firebase
TypeScript	CSS, SASS
jQuery	HTML
REST Api	VS Code
Webpack	Responsive
Git, GitHub, GitLab	Accessible

EDUCATION

2020. Web Dev Immersive. Juno College (HackerYou)

2019. Accelerated JavaScript and Web Dev. Juno College (HackerYou)

2012 - 2015. Packaging Design. Humber College

2008 - 2010. Industrial Design. Ontario College of Arts and Design